Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - O. Richard Bowyer - "Blessed Are the Disciplined", 1974 August 04; 704
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0719)
  - William Crompton Bennett - "What Threatens You?", 1974 August 11; 705
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0720)
  - James Y. Greene - "Roots of Reconciliation", 1974 August 18; 706
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0721)
  - Albert F. Fisher - "Famine in the Promised Land", 1974 August 25; 707
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0722)
  - Robert T. Young - "O.K., I'm Scared", 1974 September 01; 708
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0723)
  - Joseph B. Bethea - "But if Not", 1974 September 08; 709
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0724)
  - Robert T. Young - "Perplexed, but Not in Despair", 1974 September 15; 710
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0725)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "What Does Jerusalem Have to Say to Athens?", 1974 September 22; 711
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0726)
  - Van Bogard Dunn - "That Which Is Your Own", 1974 September 29; 712
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0727)
  - Creighton Lacy - "Global Living" Communion Meditation, 1974 October 06; 713
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0728)
  - Robert T. Young - "Who Are My Brothers and Sisters?", 1974 October 13; 714
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0729)
  - Waldo Beach - Music Building Weekend - The Ministry of Music, 1974 October 20; 715
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0730)
  - Benjamin Garrison - "Way to Go", 1974 October 27; 716
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0731)
  - Robert T. Young - "Five Minutes after Death", 1974 November 03; 717
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0732)
  - Andrew Young - Sermon Untitled, 1974 November 10; 718
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0733)
  - John K. Bergland - "Masks on Parade", 1974 November 17; 719
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0734)
  - Davie Napier - "Back from the Cave", 1974 November 24; 720
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0735)
  - D. Moody Smith, Jr. - "The Annunciation", 1974 December 01; 721
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0736)
  - Gaffney Bkk, 1974 December 01; 722
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1158)
  - James T. Cleland - "On Saying 'Thank You'", 1974 December 08; 723
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 19, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0737)
  - Robert T. Young - "Overcoming the Sadness of Christmas", 1974 December 15; 724
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0738)
  - Robert T. Young - "If Christmas Comes", 1974 December 22; 725
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0739)
  - Christmas Eve Service, 1974 December 24; 726
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0740)
  - Stephen Sapp - "For We Are Very Rich", 1974 December 29; 727
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0741)
  - James Charlesworth - "Posies or Pessimism", 1975 January 05; 728
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0742)
  - Robert T. Young - "How Do You Interpret the Present Time?", 1975 January 12; 729
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0743)
  - Theresa Hoover - "Diversity of Gifts: Unity of Purpose", 1975 January 19; 730
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0744)
  - Robert T. Young - "We Do Not Lose Heart", 1975 January 26; 731
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0745)
  - D. Moody Smith, Jr. - "The Wisdom of the World", 1975 February 02; 732
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0746)
  - Robert T. Young - "Just a Spring of Hope", 1975 February 02; 733
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0747)
  - Arthur James Armstrong - "How Wide the Wall", 1975 February 09; 734
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0748)
  - Memorial Service for Dr. L. B. Walton, 1975 February 13; 735
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0749)
  - Robert T. Young - "But if Anyone Does Sin, We Have…", 1975 February 16; 736
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0750)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Great Man's Great Man", 1975 February 23; 737
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0751)
  - Carlyle Marney - "The Sign of Jonah", 1975 March 02; 738
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0752)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "All Ate and Were Satisfied", 1975 March 09; 739
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0753)
  - Edwin R. Garrison - "Lent Is for Rehearsal Thinking", 1975 March 16; 740
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0754)
  - Berigan - "King - Making", 1975 March 19; 741
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0755)
  - Thomas A. Langford - "Palm Sunday 1975", 1975 March 23; 742
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0756)
  - Robert T. Osborn - Communion Meditation, 1975 March 27; 743
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0757)
  - William C. Turner, Jr. - "Fruits of the Resurrection", 1975 March 30; 744
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0758)
  - Robert T. Young - "Now if…but in Fact", 1975 March 30; 745
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0759)
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0760)
  - Edward H. Patey - "The Easter Message of Resurrection", "Resurrection Now", 1975 April 06; 746
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0761)
  - 50th Anniversary Convocation, 1975 April 12; 747
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0762)
  - James S. Thomas - "Those Through Whom We Hear", 1975 April 13; 748
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0763)
  - David Lambert - "A Modern Affirmation", 1975 April 20; 749
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0764)
  - Hugh Anderson - "Godly Laughter", 1975 April 27; 750
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0765)
  - Robert T. Young - "A Strange Joy", 1975 May 04; 751
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0766)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Living at Sixes and Sevens" Divinity School Graduation, 1975 May 10; 752
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0767)
  - Dean Wilson - Nursing Recognition Service, 1975 May 10; 753
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0768)
  - William Stringfellow - "The Wisdom of Being Foolish" Baccalaureate for Advanced Degree Candidates, 1975 May 10; 754
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0769)
  - Hippocratic Oath Ceremony for Duke's School of Medicine, 1975 May 10; 755
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0770)
  - Earnest T. Campbell - "What's the Story?"Baccalaureate Service A - K, 1975 May 11; 756
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0771)
  - Earnest T. Campbell - "What's the Story?"Baccalaureate Service L - Z, 1975 May 11; 757
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0772)
  - Engineering Commencement Ceremony, 1975 May 11; 758
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0773)
  - Robert L. Johnson - "Old Times Not Forgotten", 1975 May 18; 759
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0774)
  - Susan Halse - "Courage to See and to Be", 1975 May 25; 760
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0775)
  - John Borens - "The Snares of Substitution", 1975 June 01; 761
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0776)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "Go To the Place…", 1975 June 08; 762
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0777)
  - Charles S. Hubbard - "God and Secularism", 1975 June 15; 763
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0778)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Life, Liberty, and the Pursuit of Maturity", 1975 June 22; 764
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0779)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "On Being Uneasy in Zion", 1975 June 29; 765
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0780)
  - Donald W. Shriver, Jr. - "America Remembers", 1975 July 06; 766
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0781)
  - William W. Rankin - "Inconsequentially Landing in Hell", 1975 July 13; 767
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0782)
  - Lawrence A. Miller - "Faith, Doubt, Tension in Every Man", 1975 July 20; 768
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0783)
  - Robert T. Young - "A Story of Logs and Specks", 1975 July 27; 769
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0784)
  - Paul A. Mickey - "Applied Robbery or Prayerful Peace", 1975 August 03; 770
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0785)
  - H. Eugene Peacock - "Rich Man, Poor Man", 1975 August 10; 771
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0786)
  - Thomas Woodward - "For Me, Terrifying Words", 1975 August 17; 772
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0787)
  - Robert Seymour - "Shalom", 1975 August 24; 773
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0788)
  - Robert T. Young - "Just a Sprig of Hope", 1975 August 31; 774
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0789)
  - Joan Bates Forsberg - "Reflections on International Women's Year", 1975 September 07; 775
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0790)
  - James T. Cleland - "Thirty Years After; Love, Peace, and Joy", 1975 September 14; 776
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0791)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "Passion for the Possible", 1975 September 21; 777
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0792)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Best Place to Work for Christ", 1975 September 28; 778
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0793)
  - Robert C. Gregg - Communion Meditation, 1975 October 05; 779
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0794)
  - William Sloan Coffin, Jr. - "Scared to Death", 1975 October 12; 780
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0795)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Gusto of the Gospel", 1975 October 19; 781
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0796)
  - Earl G. Hunt, Jr. - "The Cloud over the Tabernacle", 1975 October 26; 782
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0797)
  - William A. Holmes - "The Beggar's Mission", 1975 October 29; 783
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0798)
  - Robert T. Young - "Living beyond Death", 1975 November 02; 784
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0799)
  - Robert T. Young - "A Christian's Right to Be a Sinner", 1975 November 09; 785
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0800)
  - Preacher/Sermon Unknown - Youth Day, 1975 November 15; 786
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0801)
  - John O. Blackburn - "What about 'Eruditio Et Religio'?", 1975 November 16; 787
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0802)
  - Eurythemes Workshop - "Prayers from the Ark", 1975 November 16; 788
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0803)
  - John K. Bergland - "When You Feast and When You Fast", 1975 November 23; 789
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0804)
  - Robert T. Young - "Our Prayers Are Answered", 1975 November 30; 790
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0805)
  - Robert T. Young - "Doom or Daylight: Voices in the Dark", 1975 December 07; 791
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0806)
  - Earnest A. Fitzgerald - "What the Angels Really Said", 1975 December 14; 792
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0807)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "We Are Not Alone", 1975 December 21; 793
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0808)
  - Christmas Eve Service, 1975 December 24; 794
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0809)
  - Heather Murray Elkins - "Caught Between Christmas and New Year's", 1975 December 28; 795
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0810)
  - Wesley Kort - "Calculating Exclusion Risk", 1976 January 04; 796
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0811)
  - Benjamin Mays - "The Second Two Hundred Years", 1976 January 11; 797
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 21, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0812)
  - Benjamin Mays - "Martin Luther King, Jr." Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Service, 1976 January 11; 798
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0813)
  - Joseph Gossman - "Our Common Christian Calling", 1976 January 18; 799
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0814)
  - Robert T. Young - "What Is the Message?", 1976 January 25; 800
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0815)
  - Roland E. Murphy - "They Came to Know Him in the Breaking of the Bread", 1976 February 01; 801
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0816)
  - Tom Skinner - Sermon Untitled 11:00 am, 1976 February 08; 802
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0817)
  - Tom Skinner - Sermon Untitled 4:00 pm, 1976 February 08; 803
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0818)
  - Robert T. Young - "Does It Really Matter?", 1976 February 15; 804
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0819)
  - Lloyd R. Bailey - "Remember! Remember!", 1976 February 22; 805
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0820)
  - Gilleasbuig MacMillan - "The Church Is for Healing", 1976 February 29; 806
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0821)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "Risk the Wilderness", 1976 March 07; 807
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0822)
  - William C. Turner, Jr. - "Speak in a Mourning Land", 1976 March 14; 808
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0823)
  - Jean Horstman - "God's Question", 1976 March 21; 809
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0824)
  - Krister Stendahl - "The Bible Is for Survival, Not for Success", 1976 March 28; 810
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0825)
  - Robert T. Young - "One…for the People", 1976 April 04; 811
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0826)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "All the City Was Stirred", 1976 April 11; 812
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0827)
  - Thomas A. Langford - "The Last Supper and Christian Discipleship", 1976 April 15; 813
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0828)
  - Robert T. Young - "I Am the Resurrection and the Life" Easter Service 9:00 am, 1976 April 18; 814
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0829)
  - Robert T. Young - "I Am the Resurrection and the Life" Easter Service 11:00 am, 1976 April 18; 815
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0830)
  - B. Maurice Ritchie - "Job and Thomas", "Blessed Are Those Who Have Not Seen", 1976 April 25; 816
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0831)
  - Robert T. Young - "Journey Inward, Journey Outward", 1976 May 02; 817
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0832)
  - Stuart C. Henry - Baccalaureate Service for Advanced Degree Candidates, 1976 May 08; 818
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0833)
  - Herbert O. Edwards - Baccalaureate Service for Divinity School Candidates, 1976 May 08; 819
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0834)
  - Donald W. Shriver, Jr. - "Renewing the Ruins" Baccalaureate Service for Bachelor's Degree, 1976 May 09; 820
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0835)
  - Andrew J. O'Brian - "Our Union with the Lord in the Community of the Church", 1976 May 16; 821
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0836)
  - Robert L. Johnson - "The Nations and the Kingdom of God: A Bicentennial Celebration", 1976 May 23; 822
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0837)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "Broken Community", 1976 May 30; 823
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0838)
  - Joseph B. Bethea - "When Pentecost Came", 1976 June 06; 824
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0839)
  - Peter J. Lee - "The Simplicity of a Complex Faith", 1976 June 13; 825
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0840)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "Dreams, Deeds, and Wisdom of the Years", 1976 June 20; 826
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0841)
  - Paul S. Minear - "A New Creation", 1976 June 27; 827
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0842)
  - Robert T. Young - "Where Do We Go from Here?", 1976 July 04; 828
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0843)
  - William W. Finlator - "Faith and Morals", 1976 July 11; 829
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0844)
  - Z. D. Harris - "Who Would Have Thought It?", 1976 July 25; 830
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0845)
  - Helen G. Crotwell - "How Can We Sing the Lord's Song?", 1976 August 01; 831
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0846)
  - Samuel R. Hope - "The Shattering and Strengthening Grace…", 1976 August 08; 832
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0847)
  - Samuel S. Wiley - "The Redemption of the Routine", 1976 August 22; 833
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0848)
  - John H. Westerhoff - "Religion or Faith? But When the Son of Man Comes, Will He Find Faith on Earth?", 1976 August 29; 834
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 22, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0849)
  - Robert T. Young - "Expectations: Real and Unreal", 1976 September 05; 835
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0850)
  - James T. Laney - "On Not Being Intimidated", 1976 September 12; 836
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0851)
  - Helen G. Crotwell or Vergel L. Lattimore, III - "Be Not Conformed", 1976 September 19; 837
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0852)
  - Memorial Service for Reggie Howard, 1976 September 23; 838
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0853)
  - Robert T. Young - "And When You Pray…", 1976 September 26; 839
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0854)
  - James T. Cleland - "That They May Be One" Communion Meditation, 1976 October 03; 840
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0855)
  - Memorial Service for Deborah Steer, 1976 October 06; 841
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0856)
  - Philip Potter - "Christ Liberates for Community and Scripture", 1976 October 10; 842
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0857)
  - Robert T. Young - "One Day's Dose Is Enough", 1976 October 17; 843
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0858)
  - William D. Davies - "The Bible Today", 1976 October 24; 844
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0859)
  - Carl W. Bieneman - Morning Service, 1976 October 24; 845
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0860)
  - Robert T. Young - "There Is a Longing in the Land", 1976 October 31; 846
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0861)
  - Robert N. Davies - Acolyte Festival - Eucharist, 1976 November 06; 847
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0862)
  - Robert T. Young - "The Seen and the Unseen", 1976 November 07; 848
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0863)
  - Leontine Kelly - "The Character of Christian Waiting", 1976 November 14; 849
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 23, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0864)